<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<language>
  <category name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo">
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_1"><![CDATA[Feed sales]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_1"><![CDATA[Feeding allowed! But only with proper feeding. Instead of chocolate and other sweets, you will find healthy food for every animal.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_2"><![CDATA[French Fry Booth]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_2"><![CDATA[Fries, sausage and grilled chicken? Yum! Just the smell is enough to make visitors salivate.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_3"><![CDATA[Toys]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_3"><![CDATA[Everyone wants a souvenir from the zoo. Cute stuffed animals from the vending machine are a real hit!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_4"><![CDATA[Drinks]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_4"><![CDATA[Coke, beer or coffee? Sometimes you need to refresh yourself!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_5"><![CDATA[Hot dog stand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_5"><![CDATA[I'm here for the hot dog! Straight up tastes best. The hot dog stand is a real gold mine.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_6"><![CDATA[Ice cream]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_6"><![CDATA[Yummy, yummy! Kids love ice cream. You can't do without ice cream in your zoo, it just belongs there!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_7"><![CDATA[Balloons stand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_7"><![CDATA[Colourful balloons and lots of trinkets will increase the number of visitors to your zoo.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_8"><![CDATA[Tearoom]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_8"><![CDATA[The tea room is an oasis of peace in your zoo. Visitors here forget the hustle and bustle of everyday life.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_9"><![CDATA[Toilet]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_9"><![CDATA[Everybody has to take a leak sometime! Toilets are your calling card: Keep them clean at all times to give visitors a good impression of your zoo.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_10"><![CDATA[Luxury toilet]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_10"><![CDATA[Luxury toilets with padded seats? Visitors appreciate this and are happy to pay extra for this luxury.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_11"><![CDATA[Water tank]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_11"><![CDATA[Make sure you have enough water so that your animals always have something to drink. And you have to wash them occasionally.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_12"><![CDATA[Barn]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_12"><![CDATA[Store feed in the barn to keep it fresh for a long time. Make sure you always have enough food for the animals.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_13"><![CDATA[Pizza]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_13"><![CDATA[Like a real Italian pizzeria! This pizza smells exceptionally good and is sure to attract hungry visitors to your zoo.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_14"><![CDATA[Pancakes]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_14"><![CDATA[Thin pancakes with nutella or jam! And true gourmets will order pancakes with strawberries and whipped cream. Or do you prefer savoury pancakes? Maybe with cheese and ham, that's also a great combination.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_15"><![CDATA[CBS Kiosk]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_15"><![CDATA[This special and exclusive kiosk, which you only get with your bonus code, will take care of a great selection of magazines in your zoo!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_16"><![CDATA[American bar]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_16"><![CDATA[Jukebox, milkshakes, steaks and burgers: the American bar brings the atmosphere of the 1950s to your zoo.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_17"><![CDATA[Sausages on a skewer]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_17"><![CDATA[Do you like American sausages in batter? Then get them for your zoo! Once you try them, you've got to have them!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_18"><![CDATA[Confectionery]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_18"><![CDATA[I'd ask for whipped cream! A cup of hot coffee and a nice dessert just belongs to a real trip.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_19"><![CDATA[Audio guides kiosk]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_19"><![CDATA[Your audience wants real entertainment. With the audio guide they get information about your animals right in their ear!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_20"><![CDATA[Zoo group]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_20"><![CDATA[You want some fun? Then this high-quality musician's combo is the perfect choice for your zoo concert. Visitors love it and are happy to donate something: the band will give you 1 zoodolar a day!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_21"><![CDATA[Grill bar]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_21"><![CDATA[Your visitors need a good piece of meat now and then. And that goes for your animal friends too: good meat from good breeding tastes great.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_22"><![CDATA[Gingerbread House]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_22"><![CDATA[Not only Hansel and Gretel like gingerbread houses, your visitors like them too. Wait, they'll soon be feasting on the walls and chimney!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_23"><![CDATA[Roasted Almonds]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_23"><![CDATA[Hot, sweet and really tasty: roasted almonds and warm chestnuts will warm up your visitors in winter time.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_24"><![CDATA[Fruit punch stand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_24"><![CDATA[Hot fruit punch in freezing weather, that's great! Set up a punch stand in your zoo and soon you'll have crowds of visitors standing around it! What a great deal!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_25"><![CDATA[Souvenir shop]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_25"><![CDATA[What? You went to the zoo and didn't buy any souvenirs for your loved ones? You can find stuffed animals, rubber ducks, etc. in the gift shop.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_26"><![CDATA[Cotton candy]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_26"><![CDATA[That's something! Very sticky, squishy cotton on wood!
There's a line for that cotton candy! It tastes great!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_27"><![CDATA[Milk bar]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_27"><![CDATA[Milk will refresh and energize visitors! These milkshakes are healthy and famous far beyond the gates of your zoo!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_28"><![CDATA[Popcorn]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_28"><![CDATA[Sweet or salty? As long as it's delicious popcorn! All the foodies will enjoy it! But watch out for curious pigeons...]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_29"><![CDATA[Observation tower]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_29"><![CDATA[Ahoy! Greetings from aboveee! That lookout tower is really brilliant! All the paddocks are best seen from here. It puts the whole zoo at the visitor's feet. More binoculars!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_30"><![CDATA[Miracle Balloons]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_30"><![CDATA[Hooray! It will be a joy! Get a new toolbar from ZooMumba, get your daily bonus and delight your visitors with a cheerful wonder balloon stall. And the best part: You'll get more zoogrosh points!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_31"><![CDATA[Sweets Baloon]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_31"><![CDATA[Lollipops, gum, lollipops, liquorice snakes ... this is heaven on earth for all sweet tooths! And what would a zoo be without a ball full of sweets?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_32"><![CDATA[Driving Formula 1]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_32"><![CDATA[Forward and backward - it's fun! After a ride in the red car, all zoo visitors feel like Formula 1 pros. Vroom, vroom!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_33"><![CDATA[TODO: Wishing Well]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_33"><![CDATA[TODO: Wishing Well Description]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_34"><![CDATA[]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_34"><![CDATA[]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_35"><![CDATA[Pumpkin juice stand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_35"><![CDATA[Pumpkin juice: a strengthening drink for witches and wizards from all over the world. Hmmm... this is good!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_36"><![CDATA[Witch's Cauldron]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_36"><![CDATA[Autumn days will be darker and colder. What would warm the hearts and hands of your visitors on your zoo tour more than a cup of pumpkin soup?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_37"><![CDATA[Cocoa stand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_37"><![CDATA[Your animals keep warm during the winter with their soft fur. We help your visitors in a different way: With hot cocoa and whipped cream! Yummy...]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_38"><![CDATA[Sushi stand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_38"><![CDATA[Tasty, healthy and light: It's not only penguins that like raw fish. Your visitors also know what Japanese delicacies like Maki, Nigiri and Sashimi taste like.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_39"><![CDATA[Australian outback - shop]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_39"><![CDATA[Follow a kangaroo to an Australian outback store or add one to your own zoo. It will bring your director lots of zoogros!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_40"><![CDATA[Pretzel stand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_40"><![CDATA[You have to stop by this pretzel stand for a minute. Zenzi the baker says the best pretzels are warm with a little coarse salt.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_41"><![CDATA[Caribbean bar]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_41"><![CDATA[A little Caribbean elegance for your zoo! The Caribbean bar sells tasty snacks and cocktails in a tropical atmosphere. Would you like a ZooMumba Sunrise cocktail or a Piña ZooMumba? No alcohol, of course!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_42"><![CDATA[Mexican stand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_42"><![CDATA[Spicy but very good: The stuffed taco is always filling and served with a meat or vegetable filling. Tasty and healthy!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_43"><![CDATA[Slimy snow cone - bar]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_43"><![CDATA[Slurp, sluurp, sluuurp. Slimy drinks to quench your thirst. They may taste strange, but otherwise they are great! Mysterious, slimy icey cocktails for your visitors.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_44"><![CDATA[Doughnut stand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_44"><![CDATA[So many colorful donuts! Every visitor has their favourite colour - blue, green or pink doughnuts - everyone loves them!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_46"><![CDATA[Fondue stand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_46"><![CDATA[Yummy! The hot, melty cheese will keep you warm this cold season. There's hard, soft, leaky, stinky or mouldy cheese on offer - something for everyone!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_47"><![CDATA[Russian doll shop]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_47"><![CDATA[How many of these dolls can fit together? Great toy and a souvenir packed up in one piece.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_48"><![CDATA[Candy apples]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_48"><![CDATA[Sweet, sticky... and awfully good. Apples taste especially good coated in sugar. And they have lots of vitamins!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_49"><![CDATA[T-shirt booth]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_49"><![CDATA[Here you can buy T-shirts with any design. Whether it's the zoo logo or a print of your favourite animal. These t-shirts are a great way to remember your day at the zoo.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_50"><![CDATA[Punch stand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_50"><![CDATA[The perfect addition to any Christmas market: a punch stand. Serve your visitors to warm up!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_51"><![CDATA[Indian bistro]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_51"><![CDATA[Do you want something a little sharper? A delicious Indian curry with delicious rice will transport your visitors to the world of Indian cuisine!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_52"><![CDATA[Photo studio]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_52"><![CDATA[A spring trip to the zoo should be immortalized with a cheerful family photo. Smile, please!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_53"><![CDATA[Churros Stand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_53"><![CDATA[Crunchy churros for everyone! This dessert, originally from Spain, is served sprinkled with sugar or dipped in hot chocolate. Either way, your taste buds will be in for a treat!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_54"><![CDATA[Public toilet]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_54"><![CDATA[Finally! Luxury on every corner! This modern public toilet is hygienic and pleasant.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_55"><![CDATA[Waffles stand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_55"><![CDATA[Fresh waffles, fresh waffles! Choose what you want them with -cherries, chocolate or ice cream. Delicious!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_56"><![CDATA[Barbecue stand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_56"><![CDATA[Straight from the grill - taste delicious delicacies all year round, served by a grill master.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_57"><![CDATA[Pony rides]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_57"><![CDATA[Hey! Grab the reins and move forward! Zoo visitors will have fun on the back of these cute ponies! Yay!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_58"><![CDATA[Strawberry stand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_58"><![CDATA[Strawberry season is about to start! Nothing beats sweet, juicy strawberries! Can be eaten on cake, with ice cream or just like that. You can also eat healthy!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_59"><![CDATA[Florist]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_59"><![CDATA[Zoo visitors love the beautiful floral arrangements! They buy bouquets for their favourite animals. I hope the animals don't mistake them for snacks!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_60"><![CDATA[Macarons stand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_60"><![CDATA[These colourful foam treats are not easy to bake. But they taste wonderful!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_61"><![CDATA[French café]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_61"><![CDATA[Oh là là! It is customary for the French to drink coffee standing up. Guests can also enjoy a croissant and café au lait! Bon appétit!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_62"><![CDATA[Clams stand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_62"><![CDATA[Clams, scallops, oysters - served as a main dish or in a true French bouillabaisse!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_63"><![CDATA[Gift booth]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_63"><![CDATA[In ZooMumba we are all celebrating a birthday! You, your animals, our helpers ... Whoever needs a present can choose here!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_64"><![CDATA[Goulash cuisine]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_64"><![CDATA[Hungarians love traditional goulash. An ideal meal during a visit to the zoo!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_65"><![CDATA[Basket manufacturer]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_65"><![CDATA[The traditional wicker basket is an ideal souvenir of a visit to the zoo. Hungarians understand handicrafts!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_66"><![CDATA[Flying Dutchman]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_66"><![CDATA[According to one legend, the captain of a ghost ship called the Flying Dutchman sailed the seven seas. He'll be stopping by your zoo during Halloween to sell fish sandwiches. Yummy!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_67"><![CDATA[Bloody Mary Bar]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_67"><![CDATA[Bloody tomato juice and spices - Bloody Mary Bar has the perfect snack for vampires and similar visitors. Muhahahahaha.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_68"><![CDATA[Turkey sandwich bar]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_68"><![CDATA[There was plenty of food left over after a huge Thanksgiving feast. How about making a turkey sandwich? Mmmm!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_69"><![CDATA[Apple pies stand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_69"><![CDATA[American apple pie is a classic! A pinch of cinnamon and puff pastry. There's nothing better! The sweet apple filling is the perfect treat during the winter months. Don't forget the vanilla ice cream!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_70"><![CDATA[Meet Santa]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_70"><![CDATA[It's a dream! Meet Santa in person and tell him your Christmas wishes! Look, a little penguin jumped into his lap. Who knows if he's been good all year!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_71"><![CDATA[Sweets stand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_71"><![CDATA[This candy originates from the Netherlands and usually depicts windmills or farm houses. Sometimes it shows pictures of St Nicholas. Tasty and educational!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_72"><![CDATA[Baklav stand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_72"><![CDATA[This sweet dessert contains almonds, walnuts, pistachios, cinnamon, cloves and sometimes rose water and cardamom. It is often served with strong mocha coffee.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_73"><![CDATA[Spice market]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_73"><![CDATA[Hmm, that smells good! Coriander, cardamom, cumin, aniseed and of course expensive saffron are a must in any oriental market. The combination matters!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_74"><![CDATA[Stuffed animals stand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_74"><![CDATA[Most of the animals in the zoo are very hairy and dangerous. But every visitor can take a stuffed animal home. They're so cute!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_75"><![CDATA[Chocolate stand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_75"><![CDATA[What is the key to happiness? Chocolate! Bonbonniere is a real treat. So you win hearts instantly. Want to try it?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_76"><![CDATA[Temple of Health]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_76"><![CDATA[Relax in the zoo - bath, massage and beauty treatments in the temple of health guarantee complete relaxation!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_77"><![CDATA[Stall with Easter eggs]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_77"><![CDATA[When the first flowers appear in spring, the Easter bunnies hide colourful eggs. Luckily, they have a cool service so you don't have to dye them yourself - an Easter egg stall!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_78"><![CDATA[Carrot juice stand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_78"><![CDATA[Do you like carrots? Grated, pressed, crushed or whole - carrots have lots of vitamin B and are good for the eyes. Finally, only those with eagle eyes will find colourful Easter eggs.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_79"><![CDATA[Churrasco grill]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_79"><![CDATA[Like many animals in your zoo, visitors love meat. But be careful, while the meat sizzles on the grill, the smell wafts to all the predators in the zoo!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_80"><![CDATA[Cheese balls stand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_80"><![CDATA[Crispy on the outside and melted cheese inside. Mmmmm, these typical Brazilian cheese balls are best with fresh herb sauce.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_81"><![CDATA[Balloon vendor]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_81"><![CDATA[99 red balloons and all other possible colours. If you buy enough of them, you'll be able to float above your zoo! What a view!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_82"><![CDATA[Slimy Punch Bar]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_82"><![CDATA[Widow's Kiss, Bloody Mary, Zombie Punch or Hocus Pocus Punch - what is it? These are slimy punches from a slimy punch bar!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_83"><![CDATA[Wishlist - shed]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_83"><![CDATA[What do your visitors want for Christmas? They can write their Christmas wishes in this booth. Will they come true?]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_84"><![CDATA[Candy Factory]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_84"><![CDATA[Everyone wants sweets at Christmas. The candy factory is ideal for these occasions. Now you won't run out of treats!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_85"><![CDATA[Heart lock]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_85"><![CDATA[Now your visitors can symbolically seal their love for the other at this castle. Don't forget the initials!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_87"><![CDATA[Noodle stand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_87"><![CDATA[Ramen noodle soup originated in China but is also popular in Japan and Korea. This soup is delicious with seaweed called nori, chicken, vegetables or fish.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_88"><![CDATA[Didgeridoo hut]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_88"><![CDATA[The traditional musical instrument of the Australian Aborigines will conjure up exotic sounds in your zoo. It's usually made from the trunk of a eucalyptus tree that's been hollowed out by termites. A true natural product!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_89"><![CDATA[Pavlova stand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_89"><![CDATA[This tasty mousse cake is filled with ice cream and cream. It's light and airy, but high in calories. It's named after a Russian ballerina named Anna Pavlova. It's also the national dish of Australia!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_90"><![CDATA[Mandrake stand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_90"><![CDATA[The magical mandrake can unenchant and transform cursed creatures into their original form. But be careful: when you uproot it, it makes a terrible sound that can be fatal! Put on your headphones!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_91"><![CDATA[Magic wands stand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_91"><![CDATA[Abracadabra! Three black cats! A magic wand to conjure up your secret wishes and more. Learn to use it properly and soon you'll be conjuring a rabbit out of a hat!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_92"><![CDATA[Sweets stand]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_92"><![CDATA[Bake, bake! During Advent, it is traditional to bake cookies, so let's do it. Delicious!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_93"><![CDATA[Christmas decorations]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_93"><![CDATA[When the Christmas tree is full of beautiful decorations, it's clear that Christmas has arrived!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_94"><![CDATA[Selfies]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_94"><![CDATA[Snuggle up to your sweetheart in this booth and get your picture taken! Visitors can take the spontaneous selfie of a lifetime.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_95"><![CDATA[The state of Madame Starza]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_95"><![CDATA[What does the future hold for you? Love? A new job? The famous fortune teller Madame Starza will reveal all the secrets.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_96"><![CDATA[Chicken nest]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_96"><![CDATA[Visitors can buy not only Easter eggs, but also other goods related to chickens, which they can donate to their relatives.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_97"><![CDATA[Baked braid]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_97"><![CDATA[Have your Easter braid baked! Your visitors can buy bread rolls from all over the world!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_98"><![CDATA[Delicacies for fish]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_98"><![CDATA[In this special shop, visitors can buy food to feed the fish in the pond. Just don't let them get too fat!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_99"><![CDATA[Fish n’ Ships]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_99"><![CDATA[Refreshments for your visitors! Nothing better than traditional fish and chips drizzled with wine vinegar and wrapped in paper.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_100"><![CDATA[Drinks]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_100"><![CDATA[Fresh drinks for everyone - sparkling, still or healthy smoothies. Your visitors will surely choose.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_101"><![CDATA[At the bottom of the sea]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_101"><![CDATA[Souvenirs from Underwater World for everyone! A giant kraken key chain, a cuddly kraken or a giant sperm whale-shaped eraser - everyone will find the ideal gift here.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_102"><![CDATA[The wishing well]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_102"><![CDATA[Make a wish! Your wishes will come true - at least the ones that can be fulfilled in the zoogrosh.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_103"><![CDATA[Stall with stuffed animals]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_103"><![CDATA[Plush whales, plush giant krakats and even plush krakens! Get cute plush toys from Underwater World here!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_104"><![CDATA[Lighthouse]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_104"><![CDATA[Your visitors will love this unique lighthouse.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_105"><![CDATA[Traditional carousel]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_105"><![CDATA[Who needs plushies from the shooting range? Your little visitors will love riding this old carousel.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_106"><![CDATA[Rocking boat]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_106"><![CDATA[Snuggle up to your precious other half and rock out nicely. Don't get sick!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_107"><![CDATA[Dino ribs]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_107"><![CDATA[Enjoy traditionally baked ribs from the Stone Age!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_108"><![CDATA[Amber Dreams]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_108"><![CDATA[What's inside a piece of amber? Who knows? Maybe you can create your own dinosaur park!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_109"><![CDATA[Choco-la-la!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_109"><![CDATA[Warm up with delicious chocolate in this chocolate shop!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_110"><![CDATA[Chestnut Express]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_110"><![CDATA[The best roasted chestnuts in the whole zoo!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_111"><![CDATA[Turtle tea]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_111"><![CDATA[Enjoy delicious exotic and herbal teas in this tropical teahouse.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_112"><![CDATA[Fish and chips]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_112"><![CDATA[You're definitely gonna enjoy this one. Add salt, ketchup, vinegar or just wrap it in paper with nothing.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_113"><![CDATA[Booth with sugar cane juice]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_113"><![CDATA[On a hot day in Cambodia, nothing refreshes better than sugar cane juice.]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_114"><![CDATA[Booth with amok]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_114"><![CDATA[Run amok! This traditional Cambodian dish is a curry steamed in banana leaves. It's made with fish, meat or tofu - you're sure to enjoy it!]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.titel_115"><![CDATA[Special treats]]></item>
    <item name="zoo.window.shopStoreInfo.text_115"><![CDATA[Do you want to make friends among the animals at the zoo? Then grab these special treats. But watch out, they'll want more!]]></item>
  </category>
</language>
